https://choruscall.com/corporate-homepage/legal-disclaimer/

client login
online billing
c-meeting
https://choruscall.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/Erie-.jpg
ReservationsAudio/Media ReservationVideo/Media Reservationdigital services requestNew PasscodeChange PasscodeServicesAudio ConferencingCollaboration ToolsCustom SolutionsRoom RentalVideo ConferencingWebcastingGlobal OfficesWorld MapHeadquarters, USAAncona, ItalyAthens, GreeceAuckland, New ZealandBrisbane, AustraliaFrankfurt, GermanyGlen Rock, NJLugano, SwitzerlandMilano, ItalyMumbai, IndiaSandton, South AfricaSão Paulo, BrasilTokyo, JapanVancouver, CanadaAbout UsOur HistoryWho We AreSpecial MarketsClient LoginOnline BillingC-MeetingContact UsConnectionsTestimonialsThe Horse's MouthReservationsAudio/Media ReservationVideo/Media Reservationdigital services requestNew PasscodeChange PasscodeServicesAudio ConferencingCollaboration ToolsCustom SolutionsRoom RentalVideo ConferencingWebcastingGlobal OfficesWorld MapHeadquarters, USAAncona, ItalyAthens, GreeceAuckland, New ZealandBrisbane, AustraliaFrankfurt, GermanyGlen Rock, NJLugano, SwitzerlandMilano, ItalyMumbai, IndiaSandton, South AfricaSão Paulo, BrasilTokyo, JapanVancouver, CanadaAbout UsOur HistoryWho We AreSpecial MarketsClient LoginOnline BillingC-MeetingContact UsConnectionsTestimonialsThe Horse's Mouth
homecorporate homepage
legal disclaimer
Legal DisclaimerPlease Read These Terms Of Use Carefully Before Using This Site.
By using this site, you signify your assent to these terms of use. If you do not agree to them, please do not use the site. You expressly acknowledge that use of this site is at your sole risk.
Restrictions on Use of Materials
This site is operated and maintained by Chorus Call, Inc. (referred to as “Chorus Call” herein) Marketing Communications Office. No material or information from this site may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted or distributed except as authorized in these terms of use, expressly authorized on the information or materials themselves, or approved in writing by Chorus Call.Material and information in this site are provided as a public service. Except for the Third Party Materials addressed below, the materials and information in this site were generated, compiled or assembled at public expense and are freely available for non-commercial, non-profit making use, provided you keep intact all copyright, trademark and other proprietary notices.Use or modification of the materials or information for commercial or profit making purposes is prohibited and may violate the copyrights and/or other proprietary rights of the Commission or third parties. Questions concerning the proper use of materials and information in this site should be directed to: hr@choruscall.com.No rights or licenses of any kind of Chorus Call’s intellectual property are transferred to, granted to, provided to or received by you because of the use of this web site.
Third Party Materials
Some materials and information used in the Internet site were generated by third parties, who have consented to Chorus Call’s use or placement of such materials on this site. These materials are owned by those parties. Use of these third party materials for any purpose is prohibited. Persons seeking to use or modify third party materials for any purpose should contact the owner of such materials directly.These materials include icons and / or graphics used in links to another organizations’ site, descriptions and some general content.
Disclaimer of Liability
Chorus Call shall not be held liable for any improper or incorrect use of the materials or information described and/or contained in this site and assumes no responsibility for yours or anyone elses use of them. In no event shall Chorus Call be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, exemplary or consequential damages (including, but not limited to, procurement or substitute goods or services; loss of use, data, or profits; or business interruption) however caused and on any theory of liability, whether in contract, strict liability or tort (including negligence or otherwise) arising in any way out of the use of this site or materials and information herein, even if advised of the possibility of such damage. This disclaimer of liability applies to any damages or injury, including but not limited to those caused by any failure of performance, error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operation or transmission, computer virus, communication line failure, theft or destruction or unauthorized access to, alteration of, or use of record, whether for breach of contract, tortious behavior, negligence or under any other cause of action.
Disclaimer of Warranties / Freedom from Computer Viruses / Accuracy and Use of Information / Continuous Service THE MATERIALS IN THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. CHORUS CALL DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
Chorus Call does not warrant that the functions contained in the materials in this site will be uninterrupted or error-free, that defects will be corrected, or that this site or the server that makes it available are free from viruses or other harmful components.
Chorus Call does not warrant or make any representations regarding the use or the results of the use of the materials or information in this site, or the accuracy, adequacy, completeness, legality, reliability, or usefulness of any materials or information in this site. Changes may be periodically made to the content of materials or information in this site, and these changes may or may not be reflected in the materials or information as presented in the site. Additionally, due to the dynamic nature of the Internet, materials and information freely available one day may be restricted the next day, or undiscoverable due to changes in the organization of menus, homepages or files.
If you have obtained materials or information claimed to be from Chorus Call, from a source other than Chorus Call or this site, electronic data can be altered subsequent to its original distribution. Also, data and information can quickly become out-of-date. Careful attention be paid to the contents of any metadata associated with a file, and that the originator of the data or information be contacted with any questions regarding appropriate use. If you find any errors or omissions in the materials or information in this site, we encourage you to report them to: hr@choruscall.com.
Except for the terms specifically identified herein there is no agreement, explicit or implied, between you and Chorus Call. Chorus Call has no duty or requirement to provide any information, goods, materials or services to you and may change, delete or add to the materials or information herein at Chorus Call’s sole discretion.
Disclaimer of Endorsement
Reference in this site to any specific commercial product, process or service by trade name, trademark, manufacturer or otherwise, does not constitute or imply an endorsement, recommendation or favoring by Chorus Call.
Disclaimer for Hypertext Links
Chorus Call is not responsible for the contents of any off-site materials referenced. The user specifically acknowledges that Chorus Call is not liable for the defamatory, offensive or illegal conduct of other users, links or third parties, and that the risk of injury from the foregoing rests entirely with you.
Links from this site to other sites on the World Wide Web do not constitute an endorsement from Chorus Call. These links are provided for informational purposes only. It is your responsibility to evaluate the content and usefulness of materials or information obtained from other sites.
Indemnification
To the extent permitted by applicable law, you agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless, Chorus Call or its directors, officers, employees and agents from and against all claims and expenses, including attorneys’ fees, arising out of your use of this site or materials and information contained herein.
Choice of Law / Interpretation
These terms of use, including the legal disclaimers and indemnification, shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of law. If any provision of these terms of use is declared unlawful, void or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from the other terms and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of the remaining provisions.
___________________________________________________________________________________
Privacy Policy
INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE BY OUR SITE
Our Site will only collect Personal Information which you knowingly and voluntarily provide such as name and email address. Our Site also collects other profile data including, but not limited to phone numbers in order to assist in communicating with each other. The Personal Information that you supply will allow us and/or our service providers to appropriately respond to your requests and to provide a variety of Services on the Site.
Our Site also logs non-specific information including IP address and browser type from users and visitors to our Site. This data is used to manage our Site and improve the Services. This non-specific information is not shared with third-parties.
INFORMATION SHARING
Our Site is the sole owner of any information you voluntarily submit to us. Third party service providers may assist us with Site maintenance and improvements regarding Site features. These third parties may have access to your Personal Information to perform these tasks on our behalf, but shall otherwise be subject to non-disclosure and non-use requirements. Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, our Site will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant, request from law enforcement or other legal process received by our Site, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce our Site’s Terms of Use or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of the public, our personnel, users of the Site, and/or others. Our Site reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of our Site or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest; provided, however, we will notify you before transferring your information to such new entity if the new entity’s processing of your information will materially differ from that set forth in this privacy policy.
COOKIES
Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information. Our Site uses cookies to store visitors’ preferences and to record session information, for purposes including obtaining IP information and browser type.  We do not link the information we obtain in cookies to any Personal Information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set — each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences — however, you must enable cookies from our Site in order to use many functions on our Site. Please note that this privacy statement covers the use of cookies by our Site and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers or third parties.
You agree that any dispute you have with Chorus Call shall be litigated before a federal or a state court in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, and you further agree that such court has jurisdiction over you.
TutorialsCareersSitemapLegal Disclaimer
Chorus Call is a registered trademark in the U.S.
